Guide to the William A. Reuben Papers TAM.289
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II. Subject Files, 1923-2003.
  - Memoir/Oral Histories (WR), undated, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Memorandum: Burgess, MacLean, Philby and Blunt, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum: In the Court of Public Opinion, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Memorandum: "The Four Handwritten Notes Produced by Chambers", undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum: George Altman, Jun 1, 1957-Jul 1, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum: J. Peters Spy Ring, undated, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Memorandum: Kim Philby, Jan 5, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Memorandum: Robinson-Rubens Case, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Morris, Richard B.: Fair Trial, Notes re:, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Morris, Robert: Report to N.F. [Nelson Frank; see Frank Collection, Tamiment Library?], 1956 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Morris, Roger: Correspondence, Mar 13, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Morrow, Felix: Interview, Nov 29, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Moskowitz, Miriam: Angry Woman(typescript), undated, 1997, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Murray, Henry A.: Correspondence, 1969-1984 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Murray, Henry A: Interviews, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - The Nation: Article on Alger Hiss, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - The Nation: Articles and Correspondence, undated, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - National Alliance: Media Forum Article re:, May 7, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case, undated, 1951, 1978-2002 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case: "The Kaufman Papers", undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - National Guardian: Hiss Article, Notes and Outline, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - National Maritime Union of America: Correspondence, Jan 13, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Navasky, Victor: Correspondence, undated, 1978-1998 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - New York Times Index: Alger Hiss, 1950s-1990s (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Nixon Booklet: Outline, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Table of Contents and Preface, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 1, Our Man in Washington, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 2, The Exorcist, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 5, The Investigation, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 6, Overstating the Case, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 7, Where it all Began, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 8, Clandestine Rendezvous, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 9, Spies and Lies, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 10, Behind Closed Doors, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 11, Let the Public Be the Judge, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 12, Election Return, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 13, Libel, undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 14, Baltimore Documents, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 15, In the Dark, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 16, Pumpkin Papers and Other Capers, undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 17, Treason, undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Chapter 18, Incontestable Evidence, undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Contempt of Court: A Concise History of Mr. Nixon and the Law, Outline (with Sidney E. Zion), undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Stone Hill Publishing, Introduction and Preface, undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Stone Hill Publishing, Chapter 11, Richard, undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Stone Hill Publishing, Chapter 16, Daily Worker, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Stone Hill Publishing, Inserts, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Stone Hill Publishing, New York Public Library, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Nixon Manuscript: Stone Hill Publishing, Nixon's Use of Hiss, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Nixon, Richard: Notes re:, 1940s (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Nixon, Richard: White House Tapes, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Nizer, Louis: "The Implosion Conspiracy," re:, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Northeastern University Press, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Notes from the Underground: Notes re:, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Oberweiser, David: Correspondence re: Chambers and Hiss, undated, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Op-Eds: St. Louis Post-Dispatch(WR), Apr 8, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Padover, Carl: "New Research Regarding the Miscarriage of Justice in the Case of Alger Hiss", undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Pageant Magazine: "Pageant of Civil Liberties", Aug 1947 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Parliamentary News Service, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - PEN American Center, 1974, 1978-1979, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Perlin, Marshall: Award and Wedding Announcement, 1976, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Perlin, Marshall: Michael Meeropol et ano. v. Benjamin Civiletti, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Perlin, Marshall: Venona, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Philby, Harold: Correspondence and Notes re:, undated, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Philby, Kim: Clippings and Correspondence, undated, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Pigman, Ward: Interview and Notes re:, undated, 1957, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Privacy Act: Analysis, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Promotions and Publicity, undated, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Promotions and Publicity, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Promotions and Publicity, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Promotions and Publicity, 1980s (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Promotions and Publicity, 1990s (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Pruitt, Jim: Memorandum of Conversation, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Psychiatry: Prisons, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Public Citizen Litigation Group, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Alger Hiss FOIA Request, Jul 1998 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Correspondence, 1978, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Hiss-Reuben Case, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Radosh, Ronald, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Ragozin, Len: Notes re:, 1975, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Rallu, Mireille, Jun 10, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Recollections of a Life: Review, Drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Research Projects: Outlines, undated, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Reuben, William A. v. Cynthia Reuben, 1967-1970, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Reuben, William A. v. Holt, Rinehart and Winston (re: The Rosenberg File by Ronald Radosh), Jul 17, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Reuben, William A. v. Seymour Durst, Andrew Alpern and McGraw Hill, Inc. ( Holdouts), 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Remington, William: Cross-Examination and Notes re: Court Case, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Rights: Articles, 1972-1995 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Robeson, Paul, undated, 1976-1987 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Robeson, Paul: Army Exchange Ration Card-ETO, Aug 2, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Rogers, William: Clippings and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Rosenberg Art Project, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Rosenberg Case, 1951-1952, 1990s (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Rosenberg Case: Government Documents, 1940s-1950s (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Rosenberg Case: Jewish Life, Article, Dec 1, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Rosenberg Case: National Guardian, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Rosenberg Manuscript, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Rosenberg-Sobell 30th Anniversary Committee, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Roosevelt, James: Correspondence, Apr 6, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Rosenblum, William K.: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Ross, Nathaniel: The "As-If" Concept and Interview, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Roth, Samuel: Correspondence, Interview and Notes, undated, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Roulhac, George, 1960s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1960s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Salant, Alfred: Witnesses, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Salant, Steven: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Salant, Steven: "First Crisis, First 'Tapes': Did Nixon Obstruct Justice in the Hiss Case?", 1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Salant, Steven: "The Widespread Practice of the 'Impossible' Craft", undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Sawatsky, John: Official Secrets Act, re:, undated, 1983, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Sayre, Francis: Correspondence, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Schapiro, Meyer: Correspondence and Memoranda (photocopies), 1960s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Schmidt, Maria: "Behind the Scenes of Show Trials of Central-Eastern Europe" (Including Additions re: Hiss), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Schmidt, Maria: Correspondence, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Schneir, Miriam and Walter: Rosenberg-Sobell Spy Case, [1983] (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Sedgeley, Carlton: Correspondence, Jun 5, 1976 - 1981 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - "Secret Papers of Richard M. Nixon": Series Proposal, to Ramparts Magazine, [1968] (Box 13, Folder 19a)
  - Seiff, Eric: Correspondence, undated, 1981-1986, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Seiff, Eric: Court Documents, 1980s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Seiff, Eric: FOIA Request, 1980s (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Seiff, Eric: FOIA Request, Notes re:, undated, 1980, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Seiff, Kenneth: " Coram Nobis: The Flaming Controversy Still Smoulders", undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Seiff, Kenneth: Correspondence, May 25, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Shemitz, Rubin: Correspondence, 1948, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Shepherd, Peter: Correspondence, 1970s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Shepherd, Peter: Correspondence, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Shoemaker Manuscript: Correspondence re:, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Sifry, Micah: Correspondence, 1987-1988, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Simon, Daniel: Seven Stories Press: Correspondence, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Sklar, Jack: Correspondence, Jan 21, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Sklar, Zachary, 1986, 1990s-2000 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Sobell, Morton: Clippings and Writings re:, undated, 1957, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Sobell, Morton: Court Case, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Sobell, Morton: FOIA Request and Letter to the Editor, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Soblen Manuscript: Introduction (typescript), [1960s] (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Soblen Manuscript: "The Crime of Dr. Soblen", 1960s (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Soblen, Robert: National Guardian Clippings, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Solow, Herbert: Correspondence (photocopies), 1930s-1940s, 1960s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Soule, Edmund: Correspondence, Sep 18, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Stone, Mark: Correspondence, Dec 7, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Stone Hill Publishing Company: Correspondence, Oct 30, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Sudoplatev, Pavel: Notes and Letter to the Editor re:, undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Tanenhaus, Sam: Correspondence, 1990-1993, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Tanenhaus, Sam: Whittaker Chambers: A Biography, re:, 1990s (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Television: BBC and French Televison, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Theoharis, Athan, undated, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Tokyo Rose: Articles and Outlines re:, undated, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Townhouse Management, 1999-2002 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Trenton Six Manuscript (pp. 1- 260), undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Trenton Six Manuscript (pp. 261-594a), undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Trilling, Lionel: Notes re:, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Trilling, Lionel and Diana: Interview and Notes re:, 1968-1969, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Trip: German Democratic Republic, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Trip: Soviet Union, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Truitt Case: Clippings (WR), 1952 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Tyner, Arlene: Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Tyner, Arlene: Interview and "The Press and the Execution of the Rosenbergs", 1991, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, Locals 7 and 11: "Free the Trenton Six Dance" (pamphlet), Apr 22, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - United States of America v. William Ludwig Ullman, Nov 17, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - United States House of Representatives: Subcommittee of the Committee on Un-American Activities, Executive Session, Aug 24, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - United States Supreme Court: Communist Party, Decisions re:, 1950s (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - University of Michigan: Labadie Library, William A. Reuben Papers, 1971-1983, 1990, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Venona: Conference and Comments re:, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Venona Release, Fourth: Volume 4 of 4, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 19a)
  - Wadleigh, Henry Julian: Clippings, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Wald, Allen: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Wallach, Erica: "Welcome Home", undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Walster, Randy: Correspondence, Aug 21, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - The Warbler (contains articles re: Hiss), Apr 1983 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Weinstein, Allen: "The Alger Hiss Case: An Assessment," American Historical Association Presentation, Dec 1969 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Weinstein, Allen: "Beyond McCarthyism: American Society and the Internal Security Issue, 1917-1960" (Commonwealth Fund Lecture), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Weinstein, Allen: Correspondence, Comments and Notes re:, undated, 1974-1988 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Weinstein, Allen v. Edward H. Levi, et al., May 15, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Weinstein, Allen: FOIA Request, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Weinstein, Allen: Perjury, re:, undated, 1974-1978, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Weinstein, Allen: "Today Show," Broadcast Excerpt, Apr 10, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Weinstock, Chuck: Chuck Weinstock Productions, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Weissbord, Merrily: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Wells, Sumner G.: Notes re:, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Werchen, Raymond: Correspondence, 1968, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - West, Rebecca: Correspondence, 1949, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Westmoreland v. CBS, et al: Appendix A, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 4a)
  - Where it All Began: Richard Nixon and the Frame-Up of Alger Hiss, Outline, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - White, Harry Dexter, undated, 1940s-1950s, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Whitemore, Hugh: Alger Hiss Project, First of Three Films, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Whitemore, Hugh: "Concealed Enemies," American Playhouse, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Whitemore, Hugh: "Concealed Enemies," Correspondence and Notes:, undated, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Whitemore, Hugh: "Concealed Enemies," Part 1 (typescript), undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Whitemore, Hugh: "Concealed Enemies," Part 2 (typescript), undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Whitemore, Hugh: "Concealed Enemies," Part 3 (typescript), undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Whitemore, Hugh: "Concealed Enemies," Revised (typescript), undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Whitman, Alden: Correspondence, 1974, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Whittaker, Mary: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Will, George: Reuben Reply to Article in National Review, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Willert, Paul: Correspondence, 1948-1949, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Winslow, Ann: Notes re:, May 8, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Winter, Ella: Interview, Aug 6, 1969-Aug 7, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Wood, William L.: "The Nixon Story", undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Writings: Atlantic Magazine, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Writings: Bank Robbery/Criminality, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Writings: "Courts Martial at Fort Dix" (with Stanley Faulkner), undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Writings: Humanist Society Newsletter, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Writings: New York Magazine, Competition, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Writings: Orchestras, Musicians and Composers, undated, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Writings: Poetry, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Writings: Rights, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Writings: Misc. Unpublished, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Zeligs, Meyer: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Zion, Sidney E.: Correspondence and Notes re:, undated, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Zolinsky, Henry: Interviews, 1968, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Series III. Files Obtained under the Freedom of Information Act, 1930s-1970s.
  - Adamic, Louis, 1940s (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Bacharach, Arthur, 1940s (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Bang, Frank, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Barr, Joel, 1948-1957 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Bentley, Elizabeth, 1940s (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Brothman, Abraham, 1944, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Browder, Earl, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Byrnes, James F., 1949 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Calodny, Hyman, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Carpenter, David, 1941, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Catlett, Charlie and James, 1938, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Chambers, Whittaker, 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Chambers, Whittaker, 1950s (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Chambers, Whittaker: Allegations Against Hiss, 1940s (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Chambers, Whittaker: FBI Files, 1940s (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Chambers, Whittaker: FBI Files, 1950s (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Chambers, Whittaker: FBI Investigation, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Chambers, Whittaker: FBI Investigation, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Chambers, Whittaker: FBI Investigation, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Cohen, Morris and Leona, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Crane, William Edward, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Davidow, Larry, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dayton, Weldon, Bruce and Carol, 1950-1958 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Dunant, Henri, 1950s (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Durant, Kenneth, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Eisler, Gerhard, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Elitcher, Max, 1950-1959 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Flato, Charles, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Folkoff, Isaac, 1940s (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Field, Noel, 1946-1954 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Field, Noel, Sep 22, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Fuchs, Klaus, 1940s-1950s (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Fuchs, Klaus: National Security Agency, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Fuchs-Heineman, Kristel, 1947, 1949, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Glaser, Harold, 1940s (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Glassman, Vivian, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Gold, Harry, 1950, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Gouzenko, Igor, 1950s (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Greenglass, David, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Hermann, John, 1949-1953 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Hiss, Alger: FBI, Pre-Trial, 1941-1948 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Hiss, Alger: Government Investigation, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Hiss, Alger: Government Investigation, Exhibit B, Part 1, 1949-1952 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Hiss, Alger: Government Investigation, Exhibit B, Part 2, 1949-1952 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Hiss, Alger: Government Investigation, Exhibit B, Part 4, 1949-1952 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Hiss, Alger: Typewriter Investigation, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Hiss, Alger: United States State Department, re:, 1940s-1950s (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Hiss, Donald, 1942, 1948-1950 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Hiss, Donald, 1951-1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Hiss, Priscilla, 1948-1950, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Hobson, Timothy, 1945, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Inslerman, Felix, 1948-1954 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Kaufman, Irving, 1951, 1953, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Lore, Ludwig, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Magil, Abraham Bernard, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Mandel, Benjamin, 1946-1952 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Meeropol, Michael, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Microforms, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Miller, Isadore, 1947-1951 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Moren, Mark, 1947-1951 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Murphy, Raymond, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Perl, William, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Perlo, Victor, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Peters, Jay, 1942, 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Pigman, William M., 1949 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Post, Richard Howell, 1948, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Pressman, Lee, 1945, 1949-1952 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Price, Mary, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Post, Richard, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Reuben, William, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Reuben, William, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Reuben, William, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Reuben, William, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Reuben, William, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Reuben, William, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Reuben, William, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Reuben, William, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Reuben, William, 1961-1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Reno, Franklin, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson, undated, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Rosen, William, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Rosenberg, Ethel and Julius, 1940, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Rosenbliett, Philip, 1949-1953 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Roulhac, George Norman, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Saposs, David, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Sarant, Alan, 1950-1951 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Sarant, Alfred, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Sherman, John, 1949, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Silverman, George, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Smedley, Agnes, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Tartakow, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Wadleigh, Julian, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Ware Group, 1945, 1948-1950 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Weinstein, Allen, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Weinstein, Edward James, 1952-1958 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Weintraub, David, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Weyl, Nathaniel, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - William, Perl, 1950-1951 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Winchell, Walter, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Yakolev, Antatoly, 1940s-1950 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Series IV. Note Cards, Undated
  - Handwritten and Typed Note Cards, undated (Box 21)
- Series V: Audio Cassettes, 1948-1996.
  - Berman, Paul: Interview, Ron Radosh, Jun 12, 1983 (Box 22, Item 1)
  - Bill of Rights in Peril, undated (Box 22, Item 2)
  - British Broadcasting Company (BBC): Chicago Conspiracy Trial Tape 1, undated (Box 22, Item 3)
  - BBC: Chicago Conspiracy Trial Tape 2, undated (Box 22, Item 4)
  - BBC: In the Name of Security: The Trial of Julius and Ethel and Rosenberg, undated (Box 22, Item 5)
  - Cable TV, undated (Box 22, Item 6)
  - Dubovsky: Interview, Moscow, Oct 5, 1992 (Box 22, Item 7)
  - Epstine: Interview, Moscow, Sep 9, 1992 (Box 22, Item 8)
  - Fuchs, Grete: Interview, Dresden, Jan 10, 1990 (Box 22, Item 9)
  - Garlin, Sender: "Life and Death of Joe Hill," University of Colorado, Feb 25, 1988 (Box 22, Item 10)
  - Garlin, Sender: "Mark Twain Social Critic," University of Colorado, Oct 17, 1988 (Box 22, Item 11)
  - Garlin, Sender: "The Haymarket Tragedy," University of Colorado, Dec 1, 1986 (Box 22, Item 12)
  - Meeropol, Schneir, Reuben and Perlin, Oct 4, 1996 (Box 22, Item 13)
  - Goldvin: Interview, Moscow (Sides 3 and 4), Sep 12, 1992 (Box 22, Item 14)
  - Khariton, undated (Box 22, Item 15)
  - Kristel, undated (Box 22, Item 16)
  - Kristel-FHH, undated (Box 22, Item 17)
  - Merkin: Interview, Moscow, [1992] (Box 22, Item 18)
  - Nagozin, undated (Box 22, Item 19)
  - National Public Radio: Report on High Security Prisoners in Lexington, KY, Sep 6, 1988 (Box 22, Item 20)
  - New York Times: FBI Report, Oct 7, 1948 (Box 22, Item 21)
  - Parenti, Michael: "Reagan and the Russians: U.S. Interventionism," University of Colorado, Apr 15, 1986 (Box 22, Item 22)
  - Radosh, Ronald: Organization of American Historians Conference, Mar 1988 (Box 22, Item 23)
  - Reuben, William: Interview, Moscow, Sep 25, 1992 (Box 22, Item 24)
  - Reuben, William: University of New York, Mar 10, 1986 (Box 22, Item 25)
  - Vasilievnna, Raisha: Interview, Moscow, Oct 2, 1992 (Box 22, Item 26)
  - Williams, Helene: Sings Songs of Conscience, undated (Box 22, Item 27)
- Series VI: USA v. Alger Hiss, 1949.
  - Court Transcripts, 1949 (Box 23)